The.
Man.
Well here we are I turn down here in the
next block nice Mr Market up there.
Lucky thing L O. U.
B U we're at. Peace.
None of us have nor that might be
able to help you out. Which is
a lake I don't like to ride alone
at night and one of those guys got
a copyright on this. Car and he got new
to keep coming but I ain't got nobody you
know where you come from. Rest
assured I know where I lay maybe
a cousin out you don't
say. You're not much of
a talker My mother taught me never to speak
to strangers when I got so why say OK
don't get so I'm trying to be social
That's so they glamorous Chafer
damn what if.
Let's have something quieted this time Joe
my head spinning and I was wrong with it
. Done with your coffee. And
don't rush me will you.
Turn it off you turn that thing off what
they hear now you know what say that music
it stings I don't know I got no credit
I don't know how it was mine or any
different country and I say whatever I
want to. Show and if you don't like it you
don't have to listen to it and you can
leave anytime you want to OK OK I'm sorry
first good piece played tonight you don't
like it some people just ain't got any
good taste. And.
I was there always that rotten to. The
money around beating in my head never
letting up. Did you ever
want to get anything
did you ever want to cut away a P.C.
a Memory or plan it out you can't and no
matter how hard you try you can change the
scenery but sooner or later you'll get out
with a perfume with somebody will say
a certain phrase or maybe hum
something. That you can't. Believe
that you're in love with me I used
to love that song it's sort of
a custom spec and you know break of
dawn of the New York I can't remember
a night when I didn't get at least three
requests for him to. Sue She was always
selling it to. Those were the things.
You know this is to. Be. In
love with. You.
And your man who comes think.
You're in love with me.
Always. I just.
Have to. Think that. He was.
In love with me.
It wasn't much of a club really you know
the kind of joint where you could have
a sandwich and
a few drinks and run interference for your
girl on the dance floor. I wanted the
piano in there every night from eight until
the place closed up which usually meant
four in the morning
a good job was jobs money
in those days. They
were soon. Made working there and I don't
like working in heaven. But how we felt
about each other well I was not
a very unusual in that I was an ordinary
healthy guy and she was an ordinary
healthy girl and when you add those two
together you get an ordinary healthy
romance which is the old story sure but
somehow the most wonderful thing in the
world.
And I was
a pretty lucky guy. Who
. Just about
a risky I'm sure it's beautiful you're
going to make kind of hard yeah yeah as
a janitor I made my debut in the basement
of blame you for being bitter darling but
you mustn't give up hope by some day yes
some day I don't get arthritis first I
mean time let's blow this trap.
Like to get somebody high on I don't think
so wow I lose my appetite for the day.
It's gone OK. I can't stand much more of
that down did you see that drunk tonight
trying to harm me now what wrong does it
matter what drowned. There was the matter
with you tonight gone. That's the third
time you started to tell me something and
stuff. We should have any secrets from each
other soon because we're going to make
with a ring and a license
you and me will be
a team Yes that's right in the bush league
I don't get you we've been struck out.
It's
a funny way to talk down but you want to
marry me now do you know I do and I want
to marry you but but not now only
after we really good. Sunday I'm
going away. On no you'll think it's silly
that's why hesitated to tell but I'm
going to California I want to. That's the
most stupid thing I ever heard of don't
you know millions of people go out there
every year and wind up publishing
cuspidors I thought you had better sense
you sound as if you don't think I have any
talent that has nothing to do with that
I'll make out all right maybe but what
about me doesn't mean anything to you that
you're busting up all our plans we may
not see each other for years and won't be
that long thought you love me. You know I
do. Believe her.
Can't you see my son and I'm young. And I
we've got all the time in the world to
settle down. Really. What I'm
doing the only sane thing to do.
I had thought of being so far away from
you but but we'll be together again some
day. So long al.
I want you going to kiss
me good night. Sure on
a. Night.
They rather get hit the jackpot
this time and Knox thanks for.
One the strong candid me
a ten spot after request I couldn't get
very excited What was it I and my family's
a paper calling with germs couldn't
buy anything I wanted. Couldn't.
Hold. And I thought of something. New.
On distance I put a call to the Los
Angeles Miss RB Sue Harvey A.J.
Are you why the numbers Crestview
six five seven two three Union.
And unity.
Continue to continue. A
lawsuit this is out of baby it's great to
hear from you too much that you do need
to dial and I thought I'd go batty without
you I just had to. Hear we're going to
hash later she honey that's tough those
guys out in Hollywood don't know the real
thing when it's right in front of them you
just stick it out Sue baby keep going
around us casting offices I'm sure
your click. Out. Now don't try
to stop me just expect me trained when I
was trained playing bus magic carpet I'll
be there if I have to crawl back to
travel by pogo stick and then. Let's get
married right away. That's the stuff
that's what I want to hear you say.
Well goodbye for now.
I'll Be Seeing You sound.
Yes.
Way I could cross country from rides or
even after hiking everything out he had no
money to eat. Money. You know what that
is. The stuff you never have enough
little green things with George Washington's
picture that men slave for commit
crimes people would die for. It's the
stuff that has caused more trouble in the
world than anything else we haven't found
it simply because there's too little of
it. At least I had too little
of it so it was me for the fun.
Of it done any good strike and. It's not
much fun believe me. Oh yeah I know all
about how it's an
education you get to meet
a lot of people and all that but me from
now on I'll take my education in college
or in P.S. Sixty two or us and I doubt
a ninety eight stamps and
easy lessons. Coming
rides may save your bus fare but it's
dangerous. You never know what's in store for
you to the squeal of brakes. If only I had
known what I was getting into that day
in Arizona. And found out
the back seat would be.
OK let's go to that dark road. Near.
Nothing to. Eat.
You know Emily Post ought to
write a book of rules for
a guy something rides because it is now
you never know what's right what's wrong.
Road along for
a little while neither one of the same. I
was glad of that. I never know what to
say to strange people driving cars. Into
You can never tell if a guy wants to do
a. Lot of rights have
been cut short because of
a big. Deal so I kept my mouth
shut until he started opening up.
At me that little box to go private
What about. All the way out with.
A fire got L.A.
. Really traveling out yeah but
I don't expect to make it for
a couple of years at the rate I've been
on rides much like that here all bad not
many people stop for a guy these days but
a stick up maybe they kept him up. By
a gallon from New York. Or LA
This time I'm going all the way.
Right through the Los Angeles. And drive
a car sure I mean sorry let me
know. How. I guess at least
an hour passed before I was those deep
scratches right and the world would get
a free copy redlines about
a quarter of an inch apart and. The most
obscene me looking at them because he said
. Beauties are they. Going
to be skies someday.
Want to know whatever it was it must have
been pretty big and vicious to have done
that I don't vote because they are I was
tough for the most danger. Or is animal in
the world a woman. Most men Tarzan's made
looks like a loss that. Certainly wasn't
a draw. You know there are
a veil or against things with or yeah
I just drove the car in. The wrong
given left to
a time I expected to be nice dodging. And
there are what kind of dames summarize
Sunday school teachers. A little which.
Was I thought she was right with some
fall guy. I mean it was my book the horses
around race tracks as I was twenty. And
on
a million things like. So
much to. Stop the car I open
the door. Take it on the AH The Duffy
sister I told her the stuff as I was Donna.
If you want to see a real scar rather get
a load of this. Well. I got
that window of duelling.
Yeah I just go in the course my dad on
a couple of Franco-Prussian sabers got
to my door for the corrections. I wanted
a lake at night took and no man
was around at the door. Get me on
a. Pretty make. Faction set and
let it yeah I can see that
now you know that box again where it.
Pain made me lose my head I guess we get
slashed. Or I know it I put the other kids
. And was tough I was just an axe
of course job kids I got scared
this out I was going to run away from home.
Oh man I almost caught me when I was
back in my dad's. Bloody rag I had wrapped
around my wrist and caught his attention
. Dissing the bundle for sure. But I beat
it when he was fond of her Dr. I was very
dense sixteen years ago and
I have been obsessively.
But I'm never a bite of somebody a biters
a. Brother was I mean I had never anything
in my stomach for hours to. Get even
with that knowing in the pit of my
belly I didn't want to be in too big
a rush to put on the big bag. First I had
to make sure this guy knew the score I
got him down on me but by to get to
Hollywood. I wait on here for you Mr for some
money don't worry about paying for this
Thomas on me and that's what Haskell make
not another you make it first but maybe
you can do the same for me the money. I
don't make the West Coast by Wednesday
the horse Funny and sad I need an entire
bicycle means daughter me if I money will
make it all right. He did most of the
talking during the half hour we were in
the place I date. He rambled on about his
old man and we haven't heard
from since he ran away as
a kid and now we happen to be from
a bookie and all about how I got roped
in Miami one ranks thirty eight grand I
cleaned out my park idea like that it was
tough luck and I'm supposed to be the
smart guy you just wait I'm going back to
fire next season with all kinds of Jack
and you watch the stink and I think
of it. When else and thanks I'm
a tiny. Effect
as just an. Oh just
a minute or change the cable system I don't
think you said Colligan wait now side
when you finish work. Shop check your.
New law and drove all that night while
Haskell slept like a log. After
a while I began the Gets with one
stone. I was happy. To not be with you
again. A long trip was practically over
had been no more looking at down the
concrete. I began to think of the future.
Which couldn't have been brighter but it
brought it with me I. Was nice
to think soon shooting that.
Amazing what
a full belly can do the magic pace. Your
. Own you. Could.
Be in. Love with.
A shoe. And. In law we.
Meet.
Mr Haskell. Mr has called.
To ask for a wake up training
which I got to stop at
a top. Star
cast one of the top.
To the. Top
at them thanks Mark. But from
then on something else stepped in
a shot of me off to
a different destination. I
pulled open that door. Perhaps
what's the matter are you hurt.
Or you hurt Mr Haskell. Starters.
I listen to it but I know what you're
going to hand even before you open your
mouths you're going to tell me you don't
believe my story of how his go died and to
me that don't make me laugh
expression and yes my face as. I saw
it once was yes I was in for
a good believe he fell out of the car
might have spoken too which of course he
couldn't even he was where I come to
move the head for his dog Yes I was an.
Instinct told me to run but then I realized
it was hopeless so lots of people back
down the road at identifying that gas
station guy and we were going to war spot
them trying to explain why and beat it. The
next possibly was to sit tight and tell
the truth from the cops but it would be
crazy he'd laugh at the truth and I had my
head in
a noose. So what else was I to do but
hide the body and get away the car could
leave the car there with him in the
gully it would be like a wrecking
a tombstone. My
idea was to come in with fresh pot to rob
it but then I remember that even if I
only drove the car for
a hundred miles or so I would need money
for gas. Besides it was stupid of me to
leave all that money
and. Not only that but
a take his driver's license because I was
stuck for something. I'd like to think of
about that time I'd done just what the
police would say I did even if I didn't.
Michaels The owner of such an expensive
car will never be worth. Me suspicious.
To you this your car but
you know better to leave
a car without wheels halfway in the middle
the road that's the way accidents happen
I'm sorry officer I'm just putting up my
top I think and the next time think I'll
let you go now to watch your step in the
future I know that alone is great but cars
going by routes and while we
have plenty I can. Think.
Of nothing particularly as right as
they found a dead man on the go and not
a bit me.
As I drove off it still raining. And the
drop straight down the windshield like to
hear. I kept imagining I was being followed
but I could hear sirens back in the
distance. Just how long it took me to cover
the sixty five miles to the California
state line I don't know I lost all track
of time but the rain had stopped and the
sun was up my specs stick to.
Carrying any groups of vegetables any
livestock or poultry. I see your
registration driver's
license is. Anything in
the baggage compartment as baggage. Charles
Haskell Jr age thirty brown eyes dark
hair and
a fine marksman on you child has told union
yes I remember employing you stay over
thirty days or take out California plates
all right off the ground in the state
a short while. Like you done on.
T.V.
. But drive any bottling up some speed
ups and no cops I know I had to get
back
a kid at heart. I was dead tired. All
.
Going to them in the. Morning and.
Are You can then ask. No.
And. Then ask. You and.
I'm going. To die I didn't.
Know what was going to ask.
Me anything.
Newt Gingrich was there and it made
Can I come in and clean. Later.
In
a half hour all right. In
that.
There was no time to lose and every minute
I had to be trials Haskell was dangerous
not have to be trials has to go until I
got to some city where I could leave the
car and be swallowed up. And.
That meant driving the car as far as San
Bernardino maybe even to Los Angeles in
a little town I might be noticed but in
a city I should be safe and. Then after I
ditched the car I could go on the SUV.
But those five minutes at the state
line made me realize it might be
a good idea to find out
a little bit about Mr Hess. And if anybody
asked me questions I could give the
right answers. The first thing I found out
was that I had seven hundred sixty eight
dollars This was a lot of
jack but believe me it was
a kind of money I'd rather not have.
And then I found out from
a letter Haskell was carting around in
his bag that he wasn't the open hand and
easygoing big shot went around buying dinners
for strange hitchhikers before I got
done reading and I saw him more as
a chess player. It was written to his old
man in California one he hadn't seen in
so many. In it Haskell posed as
a salesman of hymnals of all things. It
was easy to see where Haskell expected to
raise
a new stake for. Spoken Miami. Iraq in
years old man. That was about all I found
out from his affects and it was enough.
I told myself maybe oh man Haskell was
lucky his son kicked off. He would never
know it but it saved him from taking
a flyer and sacred literature
a preferred. New
York want to desert center up
holed up for water. There was
a woman. A year oh come on if you want to
ride.
A bike on. My own. That took me by
surprise I turned my head the room.
Was pacing straight ahead so I could see
her eyes she was young and more than
twenty four
a. Man she had. As if she'd just been thrown
off the rummiest freight train in the
world. And yet in spite of this I got the
impression of beauty. Not the beauty of
a movie actress mind you or the beauty you
dream about when you're with your wife
but
a natural beauty of beauty that's almost
homey because it's story. Then suddenly
she turned to face me I'm hard to take on
a sensuous telling. Allies but
not from the best. But you
say Oh nothing just thinking out loud
people get in trouble for telling that. But
your name in the comic they're asking
why. You live in Los Angeles now. Where
I come from back there. Now.
Oh sure Phoenix you know just
like
a phoenix girl and the girls clinics that
band The girl must have been pretty tired
because you probably sleep not twenty
minutes you're stuck in the car. You know
sprawled out with your head resting against
the car door like past I don't like
that much I didn't wake her up. And wasn't
this girl still worried. I'd gotten
over that funny feeling out here she
looked which I wouldn't doubt it's just my
jangled nerves but their eyes were
closed as the snot out of. You seemed.
And instead of disliking there I began to
feel sorry for. The poor kid probably had
had
a rough time of it. Was she anyway. Why
was she going to Los Angeles when she
come from the first place the only thing I
knew about it was her name. And that any
difference few hours more would be and how
if I forget where I parked the car and
look up so. This nightmare of being
a dead man would be over. This day as well
it was no business of mine where did you
leave this body and brain to leave the owner
of this car yet not to let anyone just
by. Belongs to
a guy name ASCO that's not you Mr Here are
your mind that's my name trials Masco I
can prove it is my driver's name is not
the problem I still haven't asked as well
it only makes it worse it just so happens
I wrote that Charlie has come all the way
from Louisiana he picked me up outside of
St for you Road gardening and it all came
back to. All the talk about doing scars
and scratches. It was no doubt about it
girl must be the woman has to have mentioned
she must have passed me while I slept
well and. Well I'm waiting I
guess was could. She have.
That Haskell guy wasn't dead yet. He was
a stretched out stiff and cold in any Arizona
golly you were sitting right there in
the crowd laughing like mad while the
heart of me. Down there was nothing our
concern. Was her. Hero whatever name was
it was just my luck picking her up on the
road. Couldn't have been Helen Mary or
Evelyn or Ruth. And had to be the very last
person I should ever met. That's why.
Whichever way you turn fate sticks out
a quick trip. I told
her everything but she didn't believe my
story I should have saved my breath that's
my greatest couple story I ever heard so
he fell out of his car safely I think and
talk until I make this
a misstep I've been around and I know
wrong guy when I see one but you do it
because I'm with the wrench Now wait
a minute what I told you was true you see
that's what I have to do and you think I
killed him well the cops would have thought
so too yeah well maybe they still think
so. But makes you so sure I'll shut
up about this girl I'm innocent gimme
a break where you left the won't do me any
good having eventually the cops are no
friends of mine now that was
a reward but the resident things don't
thank me yet I'm not through with you by
a long shot let's see that grown.
Because I DON'T HAVE TO GO THERE IS NO NO
NO I thought he had more of that I don't
know if you can search we've been told not
and well maybe I will let that he told
me it was NOT about three
thousand dollars on
a horse named Paradise o'clock on Wednesday
at Santa Anita it was for your long
about three hundred maybe two or three
books three hundred was a piece of cheese
a big girl less than
a mystic don't try and tell me anything
about Charlie Haskell remember I know him
better than you do OK that you knew
he was a four flusher that explains
a three grand bet I'm not so sure he
didn't have that three grand Why should I
believe you you got all the
earmarks of a cheap crook Now wait
a minute you're at cheap cooking it killed
him but two cents I change my mind and
tourney and I don't like to write or I
don't get so I'm not getting so I just
remember who's boss around here if you
shut up and don't give me any arguments
you'll have nothing to worry about but if
you act wise Well Mr you'll stop at the
jail so fast it'll give you the pains
not arguably that you don't you know as
crooked as you were luck I'd hate to see
a fellow as young as you wind up sniffing
that perfume that Arizona hands out
played a murderous I'm not
a murderer I'm car share not ASCO not going
at all you're allowed to have just like
I told you many make your friends not his
belongings I explained what I was told it
doesn't make a difference
one way or another I'm not
a morning I like Tesco even less
than I like you here I started to do
a what do you mean scratches on his
wrist sure I scratched him. So you did.
So your idea was to drive the car
a little way maybe into San Bernadino then
leaving Iraq going to sell it so what
you think I'm crazy somebody else's car
here I want to do is leave it somewhere and
forget I ever saw it not
only don't you have
a screw but you don't have any
brains I don't get you maybe it's
a good thing you met me good it got yourself
caught sure why you don't don't you
know what deserted automobile always writes
an investigation. The cops find it then
they get curious they wonder where the
owner is so are. They don't trace Haskel
they trace shield I never thought of that
the only same way to get rid of the cars
to sell it to
a dealer get registered on our new name
say stop at the next store I want to get
a bottle and do some shopping before
we get out like OK if you find
a place I'll drop you off and pick up later
not the dough and you're coming in to
from now on you and I like to sign these
twenty but your way I don't get the point
the point is I don't want you to get lost
I'm not going to beat about what you're
afraid of say you're not going to say
that you sell this car so you don't get
caught banks course your interest would
be financial what you would want to small
percentage of the profits Well now that
you insist on going are if you know one
hundred percent will do fine
I'm relieved I thought for
a moment you're going to take it
all right I want to be a home
a. Few Hours later we were in Hollywood and
I was recognizing places Seward written
about it struck me that far from being
at the end of the trip there was
a greater distance between Sue and me
than when I started out. Here I wasn't
kidding with that Siamese
twins Greg she rented
a little apartment as Mrs Charles Haskell.
And I objected to this she explained it
was on account of the car dealer might
think something was funny because I'm from
her using different names.
Oh sweet home you know. Not bad either.
Case isn't
a doubt in your mind I'll take the bet
you know. There is stuff here. To
. Keep the one to shut OK you know
crowd out students or there's
a fall of it behind us dollars. In
out of work. I invented it.
Some joint want to get have everything.
I'm first in the past. I don't know
why but I figured you would be.
Boiled Boy you sure feels good to be clean
again. I must be ten pounds lighter.
You must be. Moments arrives
isn't exactly the way
a keeper schooled on the election.
In the wish that guy with the
sex would give up. Its I'm
a nurse. To get one another
drink. And your freedom I took you up
on it. I didn't want to get a drink
a lot of open to. Ideas so I had rabbits
you got yourself into this thing.
You should be grateful I'm not
turning you in. If I wasn't
a regular you'd be in the pen
this minute been photographing
a printed movie and pushed around by the
cops. Such era get rid of that long puss.
Oh is your conscience bothering you. Oh.
It isn't it's wow that's fair. Is dead
no longer around to bring him back.
Anyway and have
a good understand this war and about
something that's over and done with I'm up
there for the last time
I didn't kill it was
a sick man and maybe the day before he
got out of the car I don't know shares
Sherry died of old age. Or.
Silver I guess sociable.
It didn't kill him.
The lights. In the room.
Rattle lekker ROBERTS Yeah too bad
I felt like getting typed Tonight
Well I think you succeeded mark time as
a prima donnas course and that. I wanted
to get time. But if you got to get cut
about my few things. You
should have my worries. Troubles I'd stay
sober and I've got the key to that dough
Yeah maybe you're right I'm always
right and I don't like your
attitude Robards Well there's
a lot of things I don't like. But lives
like a ballgame you got to take
a swing at whatever comes along
before you wake up and it's
a ninth and you read that something that's
still rabbits his belly ache taking it
easy in the world trying to make the best
of things but maybe that's what's wrong
with the whole world get the Professor
Pape built themselves out trying to buck
fate now take you for instance yeah lucky
to be alive I suppose ask God to open
your door if they play and I happen
to think of that you think of the I'm
tired of thinking there's plenty of people
die in this minute I would give anything
to trade places with you I know
what I'm talking about. I'm not so
sure at least they know they're doing it
for you not to sweat blood wondering if
they are you'll find lots of the stink
spell we all know we're going to kick off
some day it's only
a question of when but God is on the
subject anyway we'll be discussing
politics next year. Order of the butts
on the table sucker.
We bought each other with conversation for
a couple of hours on the number of five
minutes one of us was wishing we had
another bottle or radio or something to
read. Then finally we were out of chap.
I know it's only eleven o'clock but I want
to get up early and make the rounds the
used car lot now are about that we got all
the time in the world maybe you have but
do you think I want to stay cooped up this
place any longer than I have to you're
better it's not
a bad place they funny feeling as like
as New York would like it was the Ritz.
In the rough liquor going to mean cough
want to do something we want to be our
expert Camille said. Nobody you know.
Illness in the day in the died of consumption
here. In the DAYBREAK feel if I did
kick up you'd be free will has cause don't
come. I don't want to see anybody dying
. Not even me. Specially not you
one person died in the if you did
that's all I need. You don't
like me to. Like you.
I love you in my favorite sport is being
kept prisoner to me after we sell the car
you got
a blazer for all I get not until then. I'm
going to bed.
Goodnight Robert so don't try to sneak
away during the night all the doors
a lot anyway I got in the morning
a lot of other police. Worry
and I want to aspire. To punk
a night out that part of
a magazine too uncomfortable for
you looked up as I sleep over.
With the woman on top of good looking at.
You. Six.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
No. Not yet down. Tomorrow.
Baby. If this were fiction
I would fall in love
with her marry or make a respectable woman
a real she'd make some supreme class
a sacrifice for me. Sue and
I would ball a little over
a grave make some crack about there is
good knowledge but there are unfortunately
was just as rotten in the morning and she'd
been the night before. All right all
right I'm coming here it's almost no
time so that they will be there all day
they'll be there all year too but it was
no wait that long shot you make like to
have been. You are right it
wasn't it sure do but let's
go let's go let's go I spend eighty five
bucks in two hours to fair and they know
you can say is let's go. Come on.
We've had
a few used car lots last night down this
way what do you think we can get for those
he I don't know twenty let me handle
everything. They will get two thousand dollars
I don't know but don't worry I'll squeeze
as much of this guys I can another go
cheap without
a fight he might think we're still in the
car and listen don't make any slips and
call me Roberts that'll cook us I don't
need you to tell me that but I just sit by
and keep your mouth closed remember we're
both in the soup anything happens I get
up and drive you're my wife there I have
to go not after the day is close let's go
back to that place on Hollywood Boulevard
west on the for Jack and I want to after
the deals cause I'm saying goodbye to you
that's right Africa I guess I'm getting
kind of used to you. That's ahead but you
can start break and try this place in the
middle of Block.
You know if you know what kind of
lawyer we're interested in selling
a car if the price is right. Well if it's
in good mechanical condition it should be
both robot sixteen hundred. Twenty take
a look at this motor sixteen
hundred Are you kidding me.
It's. Well maybe eight hundred fifty four
I let it go for eight hundred fifty Cal
Ripken collect the insurance
for it. If. I do this
forcing
a lot of drive. Around
the mechanic inspected the car we had.
Last year we were all worn out we had
a compromise his price. OK it's
a deal I can I will sign the papers I have
the ownership papers right here with me
Look here in the meantime we've seen a
day's compartment and maybe some stuff in
a right wing. Eight thousand
nine hundred sixty box that
dirty.
New York town yeah but you bought the
car in Miami. Now that you bought the
insurance we're going to have
a transfer to cancel what kind of
insurance you have Mr Haskell. When.
I don't have people there. I don't see any
Surely you know what type of insurance
you carry in the car the name of the company.
Yeah but well if you'll just tell me
the name of the company I'd be very glad
to take care of all the details but we'll
look for something perhaps not you know
well dome to my maps out and when I'm an
asshole come on what's the matter change
your mind yes I'm sorry I guess I have
a very let's go.
Got me out of
a tight spot but I still don't understand
all this you know well the minute I
almost threw away
a gold mine eight hundred fifty isn't to
be sneezed at the car doesn't look for as
much as I thought when I'm selling
a car you want to keep it now wait
a minute girl you said yourself I wouldn't
be safe until the car was in someone
else's name and I could be free of
this mess when I go that's just
a graphics you're not going. To drive at
the next car have fallen and we're going
to mighty Now explain what is another
one of your brilliant ideas.
Oh if you can I make mine
a ham sandwich and coffee and do you think
oh I don't care the same. Thing that you
don't. Get this fair I've been
pretty patient so far I've done everything
you ask me to do but no more shut up
you've taken Haskell's money you can have
the dough we get from selling the car but
you're not going to keep me a prisoner
It's a good thing I bought the paper take
a lot of facts there I'm in no married.
No kids no I want to excuse you will you
think I'm crazy it's impossible I tell.
Scuse me. All don't
want to get through. No one could possibly
get away with an act like that be
wise to me in
a minute don't think you. You look enough
like the same coloring in the same
building see I was close fits the
can you almost had me fooled for
a while I'll grow up there where you think
a father knows his own son and they must
be other relatives don't have to know you
well Wally gives up the ghost he's an old
geezer any will pull through and as far
out of the letters are concerned they have
him saying in fifteen or twenty years.
I'm not hungry. And I won't do it it's not
as tough as it sounds remember you've
got all kinds of bit of
a Geisha in his car letters like I
could never get away with it it's
a stupid thing I've ever heard the old
boy had scads of gold look in the paper
their personal fortune assessed over
fifteen million he'll leave plenty of time
maybe cut off his son how do we know it's
Oprah I want have anything to do with it
. I think you will. Appear I'll
do anything within reason but not
that so forget it find yourself
another stooge July second. Build
a fix for the rest your life is Charlie
Haskell you can take your inheritance and
go away from my whining about the reckless
weapons scheme and wondering where your
next meal is coming from Think about that
Robert's Vera please you're talking to
learn how to find this on spec and take
it with you show why not but both alike
both born the same God I can take it easy
for people around here you know you talk
. We'll be free to tell man has closed and
you show him thank you met in New York
it was sick. No suppose he doesn't die
I know you well something tells me.
But as much as I insisted
I would have no part of
a scheme there was taking it for granted I
would. Neither of us got our mind on the
cards we played that night. I knew or just
trying to kill time between newspaper
editions. This was
a death watch we're here. Maybe it was for
me too but you realize if I'm caught I
want to know where I got the
car and stuff and I have me on
a murder charge Yes Mark you won't get
caught trying not to step in if I'm caught
and she realize you'll be off to. A
team plans to give me thirty. How
will I be out if you'll be out eight hundred
fifty dollars would have gotten on the
car really very early and often champions
who we don't and don't want to design
a long shot let me sell the bus tomorrow
with the money it'll bring in what you've
already got
a clever kid like you can run it up in no
time and then we'd both be in the clear
in the clear anyway and maybe maybe if I
go to court. I could couldn't swear to
you you mean you'd squeal well no I'm not
squealing seven I liked him and. Even if
he did tell the cops I was in on
a lithium What did they do that made their
mind give me the same medicine they gave
you. My lady.
Will be rational All right I think the
eight hundred fifty of those you kick
yourself on the block going away from you
take that chance. One another during your
being a grown man that's why people wind
up behind the eight ball once they get
a few dollars to become greedy and one
more. Season though you know that Roman
general he got his for being greedy he
wasn't satisfied with the final wind up was
he took the count a couple
of days ago you didn't have
a dime of what you were so broke
you couldn't pay case for
a postage stamp now you've got almost
seven hundred dollars with eight hundred
fifty in the offing take my advice don't
try for more and I'm tired of his game
let's have some blackjack and play solitaire
OK I want to live that's the way you
feel about it so why are people getting so
on the wrong things want out much rabbit
I'm really doing you a
favor I'll be out of
a jam I keep my mouth shut I show you how
to make some soft money and what they
still I get Thanks I would rather call
the cops I'm telling you kill the man I
stole I did not immediately guess you
did or didn't you know I do. And then.
Suppose I call the cops here and as in
What do you got to be scared of OK girl of
the month go ahead and call them see
it right here at least they'll give me
a square deal you want me to call you heard
me and I want to know if I'm in. You
wouldn't see that to help me if I try and
get even with you you wouldn't take it to
can you know and try to
see. Yeah. OK I will.
And I'm Asian. I want the number
of the Hollywood police station.
OK I got it thanks. But it you
wouldn't do that well wouldn't
that now show you if I would take it easy
now let's talk this over this was early
in the evening and the conversation while
hectic was at least pitched low. But as
the minutes passed and more obstacles to
a plan popped into my head the air got
to move each word coming from our lips
cracked like
a whip. I reminded her that as Charles
Haskell I didn't even know my mother's name
where I had gone to school the name of my
best friend whether I had an aunt M.R.
Not my religion and if I had ever owned
a dog I didn't even know what my middle
initial stood for. I also pointed out that
the real Haskell had
a scar on his forearm his people never saw
gets Garrido me to run away right after
but not the kids I know but his father
knew he was cut out to be some kind of
a market so. There will be
I'll find my morning's papers
anyway you would cut yourself
a little cut he kept. You on that can I
don't I can't crack my leg off you drunken
you're crazy mad Turman if you want to but
I won't get mixed up on this side how do
we know has caused such a phony It wasn't
a man so I don't know maybe just dreamed
it up wound early on and you know the
dream when the lock on
the shoulder and it is
a cute little gas chamber waiting for you
Robin and I hear it's tradition there is
no mother. Wait. There are I want to see
police. Tape do you think you'll
learn I'll let you alone your
promise to leave the phone worried if you're
drunk you don't know what you're doing
me
a promise. You
know me. I'm sorry but that's how near
opened up the window it's not high Don't
count on me not do you want to do I
do want to. Hear no sermons Hey yeah.
All right I'll open up the window.
Open the door please open the door to open
the door don't use the phone listen to
me I don't like you Robert you know
a gentleman saying he had my hand and I'm
going to get even with you if you don't
open the door I'm going to kick it down
Vera No I don't call the cops listen to me
do anything you say they're not
let me on. How bright the pony.
With.
The world is full of skeptics. I want
myself. In the Haskell business how
many of you would believe you fell out of
the car now after killing Vera without
really meaning to do it how many of you
would believe it wasn't premeditated. In
a jury room every last man of you would
go down shouting that she had me over
a barrel and I only I was
force. The room was still. So
quiet that for
a while they're going to divide suddenly
gone deaf. It was pure fear of course now
is hysterical. But they can use.
Their was dead. And that was their
murder. MARGARET What an awful word
that is but I've become one and to not
get caught. What evidence there was around
the place had to be destroyed from the
looks of things there was plenty looking
around the room and things with blood was
like looking into the faces of
a hundred people had seen us together and
who remembered me. This was the kind of
testimony I couldn't rub out. No. I could
burn clothes and hide bottles for the
next five years and always be witnesses the
man made for one she could identify me
the car dealer the waitress in the drive
and the girl in the dress shop and the guy
in the liquor store and ticket on
identifying me. And I was cooked down for
I had to get out of there.
By one side remained beside
a dead body and carefully how to avoid
being accused of killing him this time I
couldn't. This time and was
killed if. You look at. That.
I was like
a guy suffering from shock things were
going around in my head I couldn't make
myself think right. All I could
think of was the guy with
a saxophone and he was playing.
It was no love song and. It was
a church. News
.
Of my problems one song. I had to stay away
from New York for all time. Because our
robbers was left to this death and had to
stay there. And I could never go back to
Hollywood someone might recognize
me as Haskell. Then too there was
still. I could never go to her with
a thing like this hanging over my head
all I could do was pray she'd be happy.
I was in Bakersfield before I read that
girl's body was discovered that the police
were looking for Haskell in connection
with his wife's murder. Isn't that
a laugh. ASCO got me into this mess and
Haskell was getting me out of it the police
were searching for
a dead man. I keep trying to
forget what happened. And
wonder what my life might have been if that
car of Escalus hadn't stopped. But one
thing I don't have to wonder
about. I know. Someday I will
stop to pick me up but I never bump.
Yes. Fate. Or some mysterious
force and put the finger on you
or me. For no good reason at all.